Guide to the David Ottenstein Photographs of Iowa
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Photographs, 2004-2010; Series I; 2.66; (32 boxes)
  - 16" X 20" Prints
    - 2008
      - Walz Pioneer Cemetery, 2008, printed 2010 (Box 32, Folder 310)
    - 2009
      - Richland Creek #5, 2009, printed 2010 (Box 32, Folder 311)
      - St. Anthony Church, 2009, printed 2010 (Box 32, Folder 312)
      - Waterway Through Soybeans, 2009, printed 2010 (Box 32, Folder 313)
    - 2010
      - Snowscape, Jasper County, 2010, printed 2010 (Box 32, Folder 314)